// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Who developed Python Programming Language?",
  answer: "c) Guido van Rossum",
  options: [
    "a) Wick van Rossum",
    "b) Rasmus Lerdorf",
    "c) Guido van Rossum",
    "d) Niene Stom"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Which type of Programming does Python support?",
  answer: "d) all of the mentioned",
  options: [
    "a) object-oriented programming",
    "b) structured programming",
    "c) functional programming",
    "d) all of the mentioned"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "Which of the following is used to define a block of code in Python language?",
  answer: "a) Indentation",
  options: [
    "a) Indentation",
    "b) Key",
    "c) Brackets",
    "d) All of the mentioned"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: " Python supports the creation of anonymous functions at runtime, using a construct called __________",
  answer: "c) lambda",
  options: [
    "a) pi",
    "b) anonymous",
    "c) lambda",
    "d) none of the mentioned"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: " What is the order of precedence in python?",
  answer: "d) Parentheses, Exponential, Multiplication, Division, Addition, Subtraction",
  options: [
    "a) Exponential, Parentheses, Multiplication, Division, Addition, Subtraction",
    "b) Exponential, Parentheses, Division, Multiplication, Addition, Subtraction",
    "c) Parentheses, Exponential, Multiplication, Division, Subtraction, Addition",
    "d) Parentheses, Exponential, Multiplication, Division, Addition, Subtraction"
  ]
},
{
numb: 6,
  question: " What does pip stand for python?",
  answer: "c) Preferred Installer Program",
  options: [
    "a) unlimited length",
    "b) all private members must have leading and trailing underscores",
    "c) Preferred Installer Program",
    "d) none of the mentioned"
  ]
},
{
numb: 7,
  question: " Which of the following is not a core data type in Python programming?",
  answer: "c) Class",
  options: [
    "a) Tuples",
    "b) Lists",
    "c) Class",
    "d) Dictionary"
  ]
},{
numb: 8,
  question: " What are the two main types of functions in Python?",
  answer: "c) Built-in function & User defined function",
  options: [
    "a) System function",
    "b) Custom function",
    "c) Built-in function & User defined function",
    "d) User function"
  ]
},
{
numb: 9,
  question: " Which of the following is not an exception handling keyword in Python?",
  answer: "c) accept",
  options: [
    "a) try",
    "b) except",
    "c) accept",
    "d) finally"
  ]
},
{
numb: 10,
  question: " What is output of print(math.pow(3, 2))?",
  answer: "a) 9.0",
  options: [
    "a) 9.0",
    "b) None",
    "c) 9",
    "d) None of the mentioned"
  ]
},


];